{
    "subject": "Sam_Marx",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Minnie_Marx",
    "human_readable": "Sam Marx is married to Minnie Marx.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9564443230628967,
            "question": "Name someone married to Minnie Marx."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9455775618553162,
            "question": "Is Sam Marx married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9418331384658813,
            "question": "To whom is Minnie Marx married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9315833449363708,
            "question": "Who is married to Minnie Marx?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.930207371711731,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the marriage of Sam and Minnie Marx?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9077929854393005,
            "question": "Is there a relationship between Sam and Minnie Marx?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8565798401832581,
            "question": "Who is Sam Marx's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7724895477294922,
            "question": "Who are Sam and Minnie Marx related to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7164113521575928,
            "question": "What is the name of Sam Marx's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7094108462333679,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Sam and Minnie Marx?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sam Marx is married to Minnie Marx.",
            "html": "yago_25904_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Sam Marx's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_25904_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are Sam and Minnie Marx related to?",
            "html": "yago_25904_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Sam Marx's wife?",
            "html": "yago_25904_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25904_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25904_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25904_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25904_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25904_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25904_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25904_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25904_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25904_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25904_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can conclude that:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents contain multiple mentions of a relationship between Sam Marx and Minnie Marx, including:\n\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25904/re-ranker-msmarco/82.txt, it says \"Sam Marx was previously married to Minnie Marx (1884 - 1929)\".\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25904/re-ranker-msmarco/57.txt, it says \"Minnie Marx was previously married to Sam Marx (1884 - 1929)\".\n\nBoth documents confirm that they were a married couple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Sam Marx was previously married to Minnie Marx, which supports the triple \"Sam Marx is married to Minnie Marx.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}